Camille: What a lovely card!
Barbara: Yes, it’s from my family.
Camille: Can I see?
Barbara: Sure.
Camille: Who’s Matt? Is he your brother?
Barbara: Yes, he’s my brother and Kat’s his girlfriend.
Camille: How old is Matt?
Barbara: He’s twenty-nine. No, he’s thirty.
Camille: What about Leila?
Is she your sister?
Barbara: No, Leila’s my brother Tom’s wife.
And Aisha’s their daughter.
Camille: Oh yes, I remember.
The baby in the photo on your phone.
Barbara: Yes. She’s so beautiful.
Camille: So who’s Silvia?
Barbara: She’s my sister.
Camille: Is Luke her husband?
Barbara: No, he’s her boyfriend – they aren’t married.
Perhaps one day.
Camille: And how old’s Silvia?
Barbara: She’s twenty-six.
Camille: And who’s Max?
Barbara: He’s my dog!
Camille: Ah. What kind of dog is he?